Dune Drifter is a science fiction film directed by Marc Price.
When the trainee pilot and her mortally wounded gunner are
shot down, they crash land on a nearby planet.
An enemy craft offers the chance of spare parts to fix her ship, but then she spots another
survivor - an enemy alien soldier with no intention of letting her escape.
Adler, played by Phoebe Sparrow.
Yaren, played by Daisy Aitkens.
Erebus Drekk, played by Simon Dwyer-Thomas.
Callaghan (grey leader), played by Charlotte Mounter.
Col. Danforth, played by Alastair Kirton.
Kinnear (lead gunner), played by Michael Geary.
Dune Drifter is a 2020 British science fiction film written and
directed by Marc Price and produced by Michelle Parkyn.
It stars Phoebe Sparrow, Daisy Aitkens, Simon Dwyer Thomas,
Alastair Kirton, Richard Corgan, and Michael Geary.
Exterior filming took place in 2019 on location in Iceland, taking advantage of the
natural rock formations and geysers to build an otherworldly atmosphere.
The interiors of the spaceship cockpits were done in Price's
flat, in an effort to reduce budget costs.
This was achieved by building a cockpit set and using projectors
and backdrops to mimic an outer space atmosphere.
Dune Drifter premiered at the 2020 Frightfest film festival on 24 October 2020, with
screenings held at the Leeds International Film Festival on 3 November 2020.
It was released on DVD on 1 December 2020.
The tone is thought_provoking.